{
    "id": "a5c5d3c340284d7da6ebd305c86324e2",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. she know what she is doing?",
            "description": "She is singular subject. Hence, we use does here.",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Did",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "32632933a3a94a1ea70665eed1ae60fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… forget to give me a call before you leave.",
            "description": "The simple present is used in imperative sentences. In imperatives the subject is you.",
            "answers": [
                "Did not",
                "Does not",
                "Don't"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a070cd5d05f444878f7fa316e5acffef"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… your shoes before entering the temple.",
            "description": "The simple present is used in imperative sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Removes",
                "Remove",
                "Removed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd900608474a42ec811a03b58dddb7b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. harder than anybody I know.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "is working",
                "worked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "72769242109c42d7899d442bb0102f60"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a true patriot who …………………….. for his country.",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the past tense, we use a past tense in the subordinate clause as well.",
            "answers": [
                "would die",
                "will die",
                "has died"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac2d7a4117df46d6a75828fcf295cd50"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… my grandparents every Sunday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7781922a7bc406a8bb99bf2928f0e7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam ………………………. a good job.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to give news.",
            "answers": [
                "has to find",
                "will found",
                "has found"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0b8661ffe0447618dbb752fbc3ed9d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………… the job by Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would finish",
                "will have finished",
                "will be finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75c611eba3fa48ceb4cf1aa9c4f44e45"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t phone them now. They …………………………. dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be having",
                "would be having",
                "shall be having"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea22cd89e18247ac9f1159b26946221c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. to him for thirty years.",
            "description": "We use the present perfect to talk about life experiences up to now.",
            "answers": [
                "is seeing married",
                "has seen married",
                "have seen married"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0ebb3e77ce43405a8273da414db2d2f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody has ……………………… my purse?",
            "description": "Stolen is the past participle of steal.",
            "answers": [
                "stolen",
                "stole",
                "stealed",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f10a1e64eb8e4d1f8bae74461053bca6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. to anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has never apologized",
                "never apologized"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ad9b93c224a242c8ad6c45b8bac839ef"
        }
    ]
}